Ford Foundation records, Building Services, Ford Foundation artwork photographs FA1723
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Artwork photograph files, 1963-1969, 2019; 1; 2.66 Cubic Feet About 7 LTR size Hollinger boxes
  - Feininger, Lyonel - Magic Sea, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative.
  - Fialetti, Odoardo - Tritons and Nereids, 1966; File contains still images. Images are photograph negatives. (Box 2, Folder 50)
    Odoardo Fialetti (Italian, 1573-1638)
    Tritons and Nereids
    Frieze of 6 etchings, each 4 5/8 x 18 1/2"
    Purchased from R.E. Lewis, San Francisco, California
  - Fischer, Vincenz - Design for a Triumphal Entry Arch, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 2, Folder 51)
    Vincenz Fischer (Italian, 1729-1810)
    Design for a Triumphal Entry Arch
    Pen and grey wash, 17 1/4 x 21 1/2"
    Purchased from Charles E. Slatkin Galleries, New York, New York
  - French, 18th Century - L'Amerique divisee en tous ses Pays et Etats, 1966; File contains still images. Images are photograph negatives. (Box 2, Folder 52)
    French, 18th Century
    L'Amerique divisee en tous ses Pays et Etats, 1754
    Colored map, 51 x 62"
  - French, 18th Century - Carte Reduite des Mers du Nord, 1966; File contains a still image. Image is a photograph negative. (Box 2, Folder 53)
    Art description: French, 18th Century Carte Reduite des Mers du Nord, 1776 Colored map, 23 3/4 x 35 1/2" Purchased from John Howell, San Francisco, California
  - French, 19th Century - Oceanie ou Cinquieme Partie du Monde, 1966; File contains still images. Images consists of a set of photographs and a corresponding set of photograph negatives. (Box 2, Folder 54)
    Art description: French, 19th Century Oceanie ou Cinquieme Partie du Monde, 1814 Colored map in four parts, each 22 3/4 x 33 1/2" Purchased from John Howell, San Francisco, California (Missing photograph for top left)
  - Fromentin, Eugene - A Seated Arab, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 2, Folder 55)
    Art description: Eugene Fromentin (French, 1820-1876) A Seated Arab Black chalk heightened with white, 12 x 9 1/4" Purchased from Charles E. Slatkin, Inc. Galleries, New York, New York
  - Galliari, Fabrizio - Stage Design: The Terrace of a Palace, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 2, Folder 56)
    Art description: Fabrizio Galliari (Italian, 1709-1790) Stage Design: The Terrace of a Palace Pen and watercolor, 11 1/2 x 17 1/2" Purchased from Durlacher Bros., New York, New York
  - Gaudier-Brzeska, Henri - The Market, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 2, Folder 57)
    Art description: Henri Gaudier-Brzeska (French, 1891-1915) The Market Pen, 14 1/2 x 9 1/2" Purchased from Ernest Brown and Phillips, London, United Kingdom
  - Giacomo da Bologna, Niccolo di - Illuminated antiphonal leaf, with historiated initial "S", 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 2, Folder 58)
    Art description: Niccolo di Giacomo da Bologna (Italian, 14th Century) Illuminated antiphonal leaf, with historiated initial "S" On vellum, 30 x 21 1/2" Purchased from John Howell, San Francisco, California
  - Gibbes, Charles Dayton - A New Map of the Gold Region in California, 1966; File contains a still image. Image is a photograph negative. (Box 2, Folder 59)
    Art description: Gibbes, Charles Dayton (American, 19th Century) A New Map of the Gold Region in California, 1851 Colored map, 28 x 19 1/2" Purchased from John Howell, San Francisco, California
  - Goddard, George Henry - Birdseye View of San Francisco and Surrounding Country, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and photograph negatives. (Box 2, Folder 60)
    Art description: George Henry Goddard (American, 1817-1906) Birdseye View of San Francisco and Surrounding Country Colored lithograph, 37 x 54 1/2" Purchased from John Howell, San Francisco, California
  - Goubert, J.M. - Museum du Vatican a Rome, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 2, Folder 61)
    Art description: J.M. Goubert (French, 19th Century) Museum du Vatican a Rome Watercolor, 23 x 17" Purchased from B. Weinreb, London, United Kingdom
  - Greche, Domencio dalle - Passage of Pharaoh through the Red Sea, 1967; File contains a still image. Image is a photograph negative. (Box 2, Folder 62)
    Domencio dalle Greche (Italian, 16th Century – after Titian) Passage of Pharaoh through the Red Sea, 1549 Woodcut, 48 3/8 x 88 1/8" Purchased from L'Art Ancien, Zurich, Switzerland
  - Groeneweegen, Gerrit - A Dutch Naval Squadron off Cape Town (pair), 1966; File contains still images. Images consists of a set of photographs and a corresponding set of photograph negatives. (Box 2, Folder 63)
    Art description: Gerrit Groeneweegen (Dutch, 1754-1826) A Dutch Naval Squadron off Cape Town (pair) - Watercolor, 14 x 20 1/2" - Watercolor, 14 x 20 3/4" Purchased from Bernard Houthakker, Amsterdam, Netherlands
  - Hackert, Jacob Philipp - Landscape, 1967; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 2, Folder 64)
    Art description: Jacob Philipp Hackert (German, 1737-1807) Landscape, 1776 Pencil, pen and wash, 17 3/4 x 13 1/2" Purchased from Feilchenfeldt, Zurich, Switzerland
  - Hamaguchi, Yozo - Quatorze cerises, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 3, Folder 65)
    Art description: Yozo Hamaguchi (Japanese, born 1909) Quatorze cerises, 1966 Color mezzotint, 20 3/4 x 9 3/4" Purchased from Berggruen, Paris, France
  - Harpignies, Henri Joseph - Nevers, 1966; File contains a still image. Image is a photograph negative. There are also images on photo stock paper. (Box 3, Folder 66)
    Art description: Henri Joseph Harpignies (French, 1819-1916) Nevers, 1860 Watercolor, 13 x 7" (Sight) Purchased from M. Knoedler, New York, New York
  - Harpignies, Henri Joseph - Notre Dame, Paris, 1966; File contains a still image. Image is a photograph negative. There are also images on photo stock paper. (Box 3, Folder 67)
    Art description: Henri Joseph Harpignies (French, 1819-1916) Notre Dame, Paris Watercolor, 13 x 10 1/4" Purchased from M. Knoedler, New York, New York
  - Havell, Daniel - Calcutta/View of Grand Cairo, 1967; File contains still images. Images consists of a set of photographs and a corresponding set of photograph negatives. (Box 3, Folder 68)
    Art description: Daniel Havell (English, early 19th Century) - Calcutta, 1809 (After Henry Salt) Hand-colored aquatint, 17 3/4 x 23 1/2" - View of Grand Cairo, 1809 (After Henry Salt) Hand-colored aquatint, 20 1/4 x 28 1/4" Purchased from B. Weinreb, London, United Kingdom
  - Havell, Robert and Son - Dublin aquatints, 1967; File contains still images. Images consists of a set of photographs and a corresponding set of photograph negatives. (Box 3, Folder 69)
    Art description: Robert Havell and Son (English, 19th Century) - Dublin, Taken near the Four Courts (engraving after T.S. Roberts) Aquatint, 18 1/2 x 23 1/2" - Post Office, Sackville Street, Dublin (engraving after G.H. Jones) Aquatint, 20 1/4 x 31" - Dublin, Taken near the Custom House (engraving after T.S. Roberts) Aquatint, 18 1/4 x 23 3/4" Purchased from David Magee, San Francisco, California
  - Hayter, Sir George - A Musician Composing, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 3, Folder 70)
    Art description: Sir George Hayter (English, 1792-1871) A Musician Composing Pen and ink, 6 3/4 x 8 3/4" Purchased from Thos. Agnew and Sons, London, United Kingdom
  - Hellenistic, Asia Minor, 2nd-3rd Century - Statue of a Nike, 1966; File contains still images and a plaque. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 3, Folder 71)
    Art description: Hellenistic, Asia Minor, 2nd-3rd Century Statue of a Nike Pentelic marble, 33 1/2" high Purchased from Arcade Gallery, London, United Kingdom
  - Hill, J.W. - Brooklyn, Long Island as Seen from Trinity Church, New York, 1966; File contains a still image. Image is a photograph negative. (Box 3, Folder 72)
    Art description: J.W. Hill (English, 1812-1879) Brooklyn, Long Island as Seen from Trinity Church, New York Chromolithograph, 27 3/4 x 39" Purchased from John Howell, San Francisco, California
  - Himely, Sigismond - View of New York, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 3, Folder 73)
    Art description: Sigismond Himely (Swiss, 1801-1872) View of New York, 1851 (after Kumer and Dopler) Color aquatint, heightened by hand, 23 1/2 x 47 1/4" Purchased from B. Weinreb, London, United Kingdom
  - Hokusai, Katshushika - Fuji at New Year's in Edo, 1967; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 3, Folder 74)
    Art description: Katshushika Hokusai (Japanese, 1760-1849) Fuji at New Year's in Edo (from series Thirty-sex Views of Fuji) Color woodcut, 10 1/8 x 14 3/4" Purchased from R.E. Lewis, San Francisco, California
  - Hokusai, Katshushika - Climbing Mount Fuji, 1967; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 3, Folder 75)
    Art description: Katshushika Hokusai (Japanese, 1760-1849) Climbing Mount Fuji (one of 10 supplementary prints to the series Thirty-six Views of Fuji) Color woodcut, 10 x 14 3/4" Purchased from R.E. Lewis, San Francisco, California
  - Holland, James - The Coast Near Genoa, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 3, Folder 76)
    Art description: Holland, James (English, 1800-1870) The Coast Near Genoa, 1851 Watercolor, 13 3/4 x 20" (Sight) Purchased from Thos. Agnew and Sons, London, United Kingdom
  - Hooge, Romain de - Carte nouvelle de la Mer Mediterranee, 1967; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 3, Folder 77)
    Art description: Romain de Hooge (Dutch, 1645-1708) Carte nouvelle de la Mer Mediterranee, 1694 Hand-colored engraving, 25 x 57" Purchased from B. Weinreb, London, United Kingdom
  - Indian, Anonymous, early 19th Century - Taj Mahal pen and watercolors, 1966; File contains still images. Images consists of a set of photographs and a corresponding set of photograph negatives. (Box 3, Folder 78-79)
    Art description: Indian, Anonymous, early 19th Century - 1. Exterior view, Taj Mahal Pen and watercolor, 23 1/4 x 38 1/4" - 2. Exterior view, Taj Mahal Pen and watercolor, 26 x 49 3/8" - 3. Interior view, Taj Mahal Pen and watercolor, 39 1/4 x 26" - 4. Perspective, Taj Mahal Pen and watercolor, 29 x 37 1/2" - 5. Perspective, Taj Mahal Pen and watercolor, 27 1/4 x 20 1/4" - 6. Perspective, Taj Mahal Pen and watercolor, 18 1/4 x 26 1/2" - 7. Elevation, Taj Mahal Pen and watercolor, 18 3/8 x 26 1/2" - 8. Elevation of a tomb, Taj Mahal Pen and watercolor, 20 1/4 x 26" - 9. Elevation of a tomb, Taj Mahal Pen and watercolor, 25 x 37" - 10. Elevation of a tomb, Taj Mahal Pen and watercolor, 25 1/2 x 38 5/8" - 11. Elevation of a tomb, Taj Mahal Pen and watercolor, 20 1/4 x 27 3/4" - 12. Floral decoration, Taj Mahal Pen and watercolor, 24 1/4 x 40" - 13. Floral decoration, Taj Mahal Pen and watercolor, 12 x 30" - 14. Floral decoration, Taj Mahal Pen and watercolor, 21 1/4 x 15 1/2" - 15. Floral decoration, Taj Mahal Pen and watercolor, 25 1/8 x 18 1/2" - 16. Floral decoration, Taj Mahal Pen and watercolor, 13 1/4 x 23 3/8" - 17. Floral decoration, Taj Mahal Pen and watercolor, 28 1/4 x 19 1/4" - 18. Floral decoration, Taj Mahal Pen and watercolor, 19 1/2 x 20" Purchased from B. Weinreb, London, United Kingdom
  - Isabey, Jean Baptiste - An Actor Rehearsing, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 3, Folder 80)
    Art description: Jean Baptiste Isabey (French, 1767-1855) An Actor Rehearsing, circa 1825 Pale brown wash over pencil, 12 1/2 x 8 1/2" Purchased from Yvonne Ffrench, London, United Kingdom
  - Italian, 16th Century - Bust of the Roman Emperor Caracalla, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 3, Folder 81)
    Art description: Italian, 16th Century Bust of the Roman Emperor Caracalla Bronze, 12 1/2" high (without pedestal) Purchased from Arcade Gallery, London, United Kingdom
  - Italian, Anonymous, Padua-Ravenna, late 13th or early 14th Century - The Descent of the Holy Spirit, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 3, Folder 82)
    Art description: Italian, Anonymous, Padua-Ravenna, late 13th or early 14th Century The Descent of the Holy Spirit Antiphonal page on parchment, 20 x 15 3/4" Purchased from R.E. Lewis, San Francisco
  - Italian, Bolognese School, circa 1700 - Design for the Ceiling of a Church, 1966; File contains a still image. Image is a photograph negative. (Box 3, Folder 83)
    Art description: Italian, Bolognese School, circa 1700 Design for the Ceiling of a Church Pen and bistre was over black chalk, 18 x 27" Purchased from Yvonne Ffrench, London, United Kingdom
  - Jacovleff, Alexandre - Portrait of Prokofiev, 1967; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 3, Folder 84)
    Art description: Alexandre Jacovleff (Russian, 1887-1938) Portrait of Prokofiev, 1928 Sanguine crayon, 22 x 16" Purchased from R.E. Lewis, San Francisco, California
  - Jansson, Johan - Map of Palestine, 1967; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 3, Folder 85)
    Art description: Johan Jansson (Dutch, circa 1596-1666) Map of Palestine, 17th Century Hand-colored engraving, 38 x 71" Purchased from B. Weinreb, London, United Kingdom
  - Japanese, Anonymous, Matabe Iwasa School, late 16th to early 17th Century - Two-panel screen with scene from The Tale of Genji, 1967; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and photograph negatives. (Box 3, Folder 86)
    Art description: Japanese, Anonymous, Matabe Iwasa School, late 16th to early 17th Century Two-panel screen with scene from The Tale of Genji Paper, 67 x 73" Purchased from Asahi Art Co., Ltd., Tokyo, Japan
  - Japanese, Anonymous, 17th Century - Six-panel screen with scenes of court in life in Kyoto, 1967; File contains still images. Images consists of a set of photographs and a corresponding set of photograph negatives. (Box 3, Folder 87)
    Art description: Japanese, Anonymous, 17th Century Six-panel screen with scenes of court in life in Kyoto Paper, 48 x 111 1/2" Purchased from Mayuyama and Co., Tokyo, Japan.
  - Japanese, Anonymous, 17th Century - Six-panel screen with scenes of everyday life in Kyoto, 1967; File contains a still image. Image is a photograph. (Box 3, Folder 88)
    Art description: Japanese, Anonymous, 17th Century Six-panel screen with scenes of everyday life in Kyoto Paper, 43 1/4 x 111 1/4" Purchased from Mayuyama and Co., Tokyo, Japan.
  - Japanese, Anonymous, Nagasaki Print, early 19th Century - The Russian Envoy Resanott Who Arrived in Nagasaki on September 7, 1804, 1967; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 3, Folder 89)
    Art description: Japanese, Anonymous, Nagasaki Print, early 19th Century The Russian Envoy Resanott Who Arrived in Nagasaki on September 7, 1804 Woodcut with stencil, 17 1/4 x 7" Purchased from R.E. Lewis, San Francisco, California
  - Japanese, Anonymous, Nagasaki Painting, early 19th Century - Foreigners at the Port of Nagasaki, 1967; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 3, Folder 90)
    Art description: Japanese, Anonymous, Nagasaki Painting, early 19th Century Foreigners at the Port of Nagasaki, circa 1810 Gouache, 10 3/4 x 16 1/2" (Sight) Purchased from Alice Boney, Tokyo, Japan
  - Japanese, Anonymous, Nagasaki Print, 19th Century - European Lady with Parrot, 1967; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 3, Folder 91)
    Art description: Japanese, Anonymous, Nagasaki Print, 19th Century European Lady with Parrot, circa 1840? Color woodcut, 18 1/8 x 6 1/4" (Sight) Purchased from R.E. Lewis, San Francisco, California
  - Japanese, Anonymous, Nagasaki Print, 19th Century - Foreigner with Tall Hat and Cane, 1967; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 3, Folder 92)
    Art description: Japanese, Anonymous, Nagasaki Print, 19th Century Foreigner with Tall Hat and Cane, circa 1840? Color woodcut, 17 3/4 x 6 3/8" (Sight) Purchased from R.E. Lewis, San Francisco, California
  - Kip, Johannes - A Prospect of Westminster/A Prospect of the City of London, 1967; File contains still images. Images consists of a set of photographs and a corresponding set of photograph negatives. (Box 3, Folder 93)
    Art description: Johannes Kip (Dutch, 1653-1722) A Prospect of Westminster; A Prospect of the City of London, 1715 Engraving, 20 3/4 x 92 1/2" Purchased from B. Weinreb, London, United Kingdom
  - Kirchner, Ernest Ludwig - An Alpine Village in Winter, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 3, Folder 94)
    Art description: Ernest Ludwig Kirchner (German, 1880-1938) An Alpine Village in Winter Watercolor, 13 3/4 x 19 1/4" Purchased from Schaeffer Galleries, New York, New York
  - Klee, Paul - bewegtes Stilleben, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of photographs and a photograph negative. (Box 3, Folder 95)
    Art description: Paul Klee (Swiss-German, 1879-1940) bewegtes Stilleben, 1924 Pencil, 8 7/8 x 11 1/4" Purchased from Galerie Rosengart, Lucerne, Switzerland
  - Klee, Paul - Stoerung durch Fliehende, 1965-1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 3, Folder 96)
    Art description: Paul Klee (Swiss-German, 1879-1940) Stoerung durch Fliehende, 1932 Pen and ink, 12 1/2 x 15 7/8" (Sight) Purchased from Galerie Rosengart, Lucerne, Switzerland
  - Klee, Paul - Schneckenpost, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 3, Folder 97)
    Art description: Paul Klee (Swiss-German, 1879-1940) Schneckenpost, 1937 Oil zinc-white on paper, 7 x 11" Purchased from Galerie Rosengart, Lucerne, Switzerland
  - Kobell, Wilhem von - Solider on Horseback, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 3, Folder 98)
    Art description: Wilhelm von Kobell (German, 1766-1855) Soldier on Horseback Watercolor and pencil, 13 3/4 x 9 3/4" Purchased from Mrs. Walter Feilchenfeldt, Zurich, Switzerland
  - Kokoschka, Oskar - Pigeon, 1967; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 3, Folder 99)
    Art description: Oskar Kokoschka (Austrian, born 1886) Pigeon, 1940 Watercolor, 17 1/2 x 23 1/2" Purchased from Feilchenfeldt, Zurich, Switzerland
  - Kokoschka, Oskar - Girl reading, 1966; File contains a still image. Image is a photograph negative. There is also an image on photo stock paper. (Box 3, Folder 100)
    Art description: Oskar Kokoschka (Austrian, born 1886) Girl reading, 1920-1922 Watercolor, chalk and crayon, 23 5/8 x 19 7/8" (Sight) Purchased from Purchased from Marlborough-Gerson, New York, New York
  - Kokoschka, Oskar - Lobster, 1967; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 4, Folder 101)
    Art description: Oskar Kokoschka (Austrian, born 1886) Lobster, 1946 Watercolor, 18 3/8 x 23 3/4" Purchased from Feilchenfeldt, Zurich, Switzerland
  - Korn, W. - Views of Japan, China, and Siam, 1967; File contains still images. Images consists of a set of photographs and a corresponding set of photograph negatives. (Box 4, Folder 102-103)
    Art description: W. Korn (German, 19th Century) Views of Japan, China, and Siam, 1870 - 1. Yeddo (No. 5) Colored lithograph, 10 1/2 x 16" - 2. Yeddo (No. 11) Colored lithograph, 10 x 18 5/8" - 3. Yeddo (No. 12) Colored lithograph, 10 3/4 x 18 5/8" - 4. Yeddo (No. 21) Colored lithograph, 12 1/16 x 18 1/2" - 5. Yokohama-Kanagava (No. 6) Colored lithograph, 10 x 18 3/8" - 6. Ikegami (No. 22) Colored lithograph, 10 3/4 x 18" - 7. Nangasaki (No. 29) Colored lithograph, 13 x 18 1/4" - 8. Nangasaki (No. 30) Colored lithograph, 13 3/8 x 18 1/8" - 9. Tientsin (No. 35) Colored lithograph, 12 1/2 x 18 1/8" - 10. Tientsin (No. 36) Colored lithograph, 12 1/2 x 17 7/8" - 11. Tientsin (No. 37) Colored lithograph, 11 3/4 x 17 3/4" - 12. Peking (No. 41) Colored lithograph, 11 3/4 x 18" - 13. Peking (No. 45) Colored lithograph, 11 1/2 x 18" - 14. Peking (No. 46) Colored lithograph, 12 1/2 x 18" - 15. Macao (No. 50) Colored lithograph, 12 3/8 x 17 7/8" - 16. Macao (No. 51) Colored lithograph, 12 1/2 x 18 3/16" - 17. Bangkok (No. 59) Colored lithograph, 11 1/4 x 18 1/2" - 18. Bangkok (No. 60) Colored lithograph, 11 7/16 x 18 1/2" Purchased from B. Weinreb, London, United Kingdom
  - Kuchel, Charles C. and Emil Dresel - Scotts Bar and French Bar, on Scotts River, Siskiyou County, California, 1966; File contains a still image. Image is a photograph negative. (Box 4, Folder 104)
    Art description: Charles C. Kuchel and Emil Dresel (American, active 1853-1866) Scotts Bar and French Bar, on Scotts River, Siskiyou County, California, 1856 Lithograph, 20 x 28" Purchased from John Howell, San Francisco, California
  - Kuniyoshi, Utagawa- Nichiren Praying for Rain, 1967; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 4, Folder 105)
    Art description: Utagawa Kuniyoshi (Japanese, 1798-1861) Nichiren Praying for Rain, circa 1835-1836 (From series Abridged Biography of Nichiren) Color woodcut, 8 3/4 x 13 5/8" plus margins Purchased from R.E. Lewis, San Francisco, California
  - Laurens, Henri - Femme couchee de dos, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and photograph negatives. (Box 4, Folder 106)
    Art description: Henri Laurens (French, 1885-1954) Femme couchee de dos, 1921 Bronze relief, 5 1/2 x 15 3/8" Purchased from Galerie Rosengart, Lucerne, Switzerland
  - Le Prince, Jean Baptiste - The Carthusian Convent of San Elmo near Naples, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 4, Folder 107)
    Art description: Le Prince, Jean Baptiste (French, 1733-1781) The Carthusian Convent of San Elmo near Naples Red chalk, 9 3/4 x 15 3/4" Purchased from Bernard Houthakker, Amsterdam, Netherlands
  - Lear, Edward - Hajar Em Nidra, 1966; File contains a still image. Image is a photograph negative. There is also an image on photo stock paper. (Box 4, Folder 108)
    Art description: Edward Lear (English, 1812-1888) Hajar Em Nidra. Krendy. March 4, 1866 Pen and watercolor, 8 1/4 x 17 3/4" (Sight) Purchased from Robert Frank, London, United Kingdom
  - Lear, Edward - Bishop and Supplicant, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 4, Folder 109)
    Art description: Edward Lear (English, 1812-1888) Bishop and Supplicant Pen and ink, 4 5/16 x 6 13/16" Purchased from Durlacher Bros., New York, New York
  - Lecomte, Paul - St. Servan, 1966; File contains still images. Images consist of a photograph and a photograph negative. (Box 4, Folder 110)